Guide to the Trinity College Historical Society Collection, [1492?] - 1981 UA.31.12.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Artifacts, [1492?]-1918
  - Seal used on old North Carolina land grant, undated (Oversize-box 22, Folder 209)
  - Two quivers, quiver caps, and arrows from the Fiji Islands, undated (Oversize-box 23)
  - Bow from the Fiji Islands, undated (Oversize-box 24)